export default data = [
  {
      question: "What a small computer!  Does it really ______ ?",
      options: ["bite","type","work","use"],
      correct_option: "work"
  },
  {
      question: "For your own ______ , please don't open the door until the train fully stops",
      options: ["humanity","safety","liberty","vanity"],
      correct_option: "safety"
  },
  {
      question: "Peter told Marie that he couldn't attend her birthday party because he had been ______ engaged",
      options: ["necessarily","previously","cautiously","possibly"],
      correct_option: "previously"
  },
  {
      question: "For hours, we have heard nothing but negative criticism.  Why can't you say something more ______ ?",
      options: ["ambitious","synthetic","determined","constructive"],
      correct_option: "constructive"
  },
  {
      question: "This library is famous for its wide ______ of books.  You can find books on any topic you are interested in",
      options: ["technology","connection","variety","amazement"],
      correct_option: "variety"
  },
  {
      question: "The child was ______ .  He just sat there and waited for something to happen",
      options: ["passive","expressive","extensive","persuasive"],
      correct_option: "passive"
  },
  {
      question: "After dinner, Richard offered to pay the bill, but May insisted that they do it ______",
      options: ["generously","separately","completely","extensively"],
      correct_option: "separately"
  },
  {
      question: "This TV program will ______ young viewers' understanding of the changing world",
      options: ["broaden","soften","tighten","lengthen"],
      correct_option: "broaden"
  },
  {
      question: "I like everything about the apartment ______ the rent.  It is too expensive",
      options: ["as for","except for","instead of","in place of"],
      correct_option: "except for"
  },
  {
      question: "______ all the newspaper and television attention, the problem of child abuse has become well-known",
      options: ["As a result of","Apart from","In addition to","Regardless of"],
      correct_option: "As a result of"
  },
  {
      question: "Tim: Someone left a schoolbag on the bus. Sam: See if ______ a name inside the bag",
      options: ["it was","this has","there is","they had"],
      correct_option: "there is"
  },
  {
      question: "Joe: ______ you come to our party tonight? Sue: No, but I wish I could",
      options: ["Must","Shall","Can","May"],
      correct_option: "Can"
  },
  {
      question: "Jack: I wish I were a millionaire.  I could buy whatever I want. Jane: Well, it may be true. ______ we must bear in mind that the love of money is also the root of all evil",
      options: ["So","Or","For","But"],
      correct_option: "But"
  },
  {
      question: "Tony: May I have some more coffee, please? Anne: I'm sorry, but there doesn't seem to be",
      options: ["left any","any left","leaving any","any leaving"],
      correct_option: "any left"
  },
  {
      question: "Tom: I was looking for John all afternoon.  Where was he? Pete: I don't know.  He ______ to a movie",
      options: ["would go","might go","would have gone","might have gone"],
      correct_option: "might have gone"
  },
]
